[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "Which vegetable can be sweet or bitter?",
   "Answer": "Pepper"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "Which vegetable is used to make ketchup?",
   "Answer": "Tomato"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest vegetable?",
   "Answer": "Pumpkin"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "Cannonball, bok choy, savoy, kohlrabi, red drumhead are all types of...",
   "Answer": "Cabbage"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "Name a vegetable that is rich in vitamin A.",
   "Answer": "Carrot"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "These plants are often called “alternative meat” because they are rich in protein.",
   "Answer": "Peas and beans or legumes"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "The main ingredient in mash and French fries.",
   "Answer": "Potato"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "Where did tomatoes originate from?",
   "Answer": "America"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What are wild onions called?",
   "Answer": "Bear s leek"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "Which vegetable makes your eyes tear when you peel it?",
   "Answer": "Onion"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is another name for passion fruit?",
   "Answer": "Maracuya"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "Which fruit tree is considered to be sacred in India?",
   "Answer": "Mango"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Which fruits, also called “Indian apples”, were imported into Europe by Alexander the Great’s warriors?",
   "Answer": "Lemons"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "In which year did plants began to be classified into fruits and vegetables?",
   "Answer": "1705"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "How do pineapples grow?",
   "Answer": "On the ground"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "Which region produces the most apples?",
   "Answer": "Central Asia"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "How long was the longest apple peel, recorded in the Guinness Book of Records?",
   "Answer": "52 meters"
 }
]